couponhaat.in 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy | Couponhaat.in

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey or fill out a form.

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number, company name, VAT ID, physical address and whatever information is required to complete the action. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails

The email address you provide will only be used to send you information and updates.  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you submit or access your personal information. Also, we do not collect any financial information such as credit card number or your bank account information.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to help us remember your previous actions and preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better website experiences and tools in the future.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

### Third party links

We regularly include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies, please be sure to check them out before engaging in any action on their website. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these partner sites.

### Online Privacy Policy

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

### Terms of Service

Please also visit our Terms of Service page establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

### Your Consent

By visiting and using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the email below.

  * **Email:**
